ABOUT ME

With 8 years of experience in customerexperience industries, highly motivated person that can problem solving successfully with excellent communication skills that have enabled me to connect and build trust with clients. While improving client interaction and increasing sales I believe that strong communication is important and I have a passion to be the person to build, provide solutions inspire people to follow.

EDUCATION

UX/UI Boot Camp University of Toronto School of Continuing Studies | Certificate Toronto, ON Dec 2021 - Jun 2022

Cosmetic Techniques and Management Seneca College | Diploma Toronto, ON Jan 2017 - Apr 2018

Certificate of Make-up Artistry MBC Academy Beauty School Gangnam | 2nd grade, 3rd grade Seoul, South Korea | Jun - Sept 2013

ACHIEVEMNTS

Sephora Win Value In Action | employee of the month Top mobile seller of the year

PROJECTS

Seneca Fashion Show 2018 Lead makeup artist

In charge of coaching and training Ensured makeup standards were met Oversee makeup direction for models Planned and delegated tasks to ensure schedules were met

EXPERIENCE

Skincare Consultant

Sephora

Toronto, ON | Aug 2018 - Present

Acted as a brand ambassador to increase awareness and sales for numerous brands

Assisted in executing new marketing ideas for campaigns Trained team members in monthly LP ambassador presentations for new safety and store protocols Monitor inventory shrinkage and work with leadership to minimize shrink

Promoted best practices for skincare and makeup routines

Make-up Artist

MAC Cosmetics

Vancouver, BC | Nov 2015 - June 2016

Provided counter sales and ensured accuracy is met each transaction

Achieved consistent sales goals and met daily quotas Advised clients about product offerings that suit their needs and goals

Quality Control Operator LG Displays

Gyeonggi-do, South Korea | Oct 2010 – March 2013

Inspected quality of display signs to solve signal problems Assessed training needs for new employees in junior & intermediate roles

Communicated with engineers and supervisors to ensure improved performance of product

SKILLS

Strong Verbal and Written Communication Skills Client Services

Figma

Miro

Invision

HTML

CSS

Fluent in Korean